Robert R. Simmons Papers
© 2007 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Files, undated, 1991-2006
  - Subject Files (Visiting Nurses - Youth Issues), Press releases, Legislative Activities, undated, 1991-1999 (Box 156)
    - Legislative Activity, undated
      - Legislation, 1995
      - Legislation (I-II), 1996
      - Issues, Legislative proposals (I-II), 1998
      - Legislation, 1998
      - Legislation, 1999
  - Legislative activity, constituent recognitions and requests, undated, 1999-2006 (Box 157)
    - Special session: Adriaen's Landing, 1999; [2 folders]
    - Session, 2000
    - Bills, 2000
    - Certificates, 2003; [3 folders]
    - Certificates, 2006; [2 folders]
    - CCOM, 2004-2005; [2 folderes]
    - Eagle Scouts, 2001; [2 folders]
    - Forms completed
      - Washington, DC, 2001
      - Requests, 2001
      - Requests, 2002-2003
      - Buck, 2001-2002
      - Flags, 2001-2003
      - Greetings, 2001-2003
      - Casework, 2001
  - Phone message books, 2001-2006 (Box 158)
    - Al's messages books, 2001-2006
    - Staff message books, 2001-2002
  - Issue forms, 2002-2004 (Box 159)
    - I-IV, 2003; [4 folders]
    - I-II, 2004; [2 folders]
    - V-X, 2003; [6 folders]
    - 2002-2003
    - I-VIII, 2002; [8 folders]
  - Issue forms, 2001-2002 (Box 160)
    - IX-XIV, 2002; [6 folders]
    - I-XIV, 2001; [14 folders]
  - Issues (inlcudes 109th Congress), 2002-2007 (Box 161)
    - Commercial fishing, undated; [3 folders]
    - Telecommunications and campaign finance, undated
    - Agriculture, undated
    - Farmers, undated
      - Kofkoff
      - Farm Bill
      - Betty
      - Manure and CERCLA
      - Farm credit
    - Energey and Water appropriations, 2004, 2006
    - Appropriations, 2007
      - Interior
      - E & W
      - QSHC
      - Johnson tract
      - Menunketesuck Salt Meadow marsh
      - Enfield sewer project
      - Sprague
      - Colchester water extension project
      - Groton water extension project
      - East Hampton wastewater improvements
      - Seaport 2
      - North Cove (Connecticut River below Hartford, CT
      - Nystic dredge project
      - Aquarium
      - Thames River pipeline
      - Enfield I-91 flooding
      - Seaport
      - Norwich Public utilities
      - Shaw's Cove drainage restoration
      - NO-GOs
      - FY 2007 appropriations
      - NECTER
    - Labor, undated
      - Davis-Bacon
      - Department of labor overtime regulations
      - AFL-CIO
      - Boilermakers
      - Compensatory time HR 1119
  - Labor and Indians, undated, 2004-2005 (Box 162)
    - Labor, undated, 2005
      - Postal, undated
      - NTEU, undated
      - National Right to Work, undated
      - Pratt, undated
      - Tax Priv. amendment, undated
      - SBC/CWA, undated
      - TTD, undated
      - UConn task force, undated
      - UAW/MDA, undated
      - SCSEP, undated
      - Workforce Reinvestment, HR 1261, undated
      - Waterbury Workforce grant, undated
      - GOP Labor caucus, undated
      - Marine One, undated
      - J. Martin--NTEU, undated
      - OSHA Buills--HR 2728-2731, undated
      - Pay Party--HRes. 581, undated
      - LM-2, undated
      - FAA/ATC, undated
      - Firefighters, undated
      - IUC Conference, 2005 May 10
    - Indians, undated, 2004-2005
      - Schagticoke
      - Golden Hills Paugussett, undated
      - Senate hearing, 2005 May 11
      - G.R. hearing, 2004 May 5
      - UConn Indian Law, undated
      - Nipmucs, undated
      - Indians, undated
      - BIA reform, undated
      - Clippings, undated
      - Eastern Pequot, undated
  - Issues (108th-109th Congress), undated, 2001-2003 (Box 163)
    - Backus Hospital Whistleblower, undated; [2 folders]
    - Abortion, undated
    - Medicare and Medicaid, undated; [2 ff]
    - Veterans, undated
    - Housing, undated
    - Welfare/Children's Issues, undated
    - Bills, Dear Colleagues, Sign-on letters, undated
    - Social Security, undated
    - Hiram Bingham IV Stamp, undated; [3 ff]
    - Sock Monkey information, undated
    - UConn resolutions, undated
    - Eminent domain, New London, undated
    - Cancer cuts, undated
    - Nathan Hale, undated
    - Supportive Housing letter information, undated
    - Plum Island, undated; [2 ff]
    - Remarks for National Association of State Veterans Homes, undated
    - Robo calls, undated
    - New London CHC, undated
    - H.R. 2296--Federal no frills prison act of 2003, undated
    - Cyber molesters, undated
    - VOCA/VAWA, undated
    - Medicare articles, undated
    - Emergency contraceptives, undated
    - Big Brothers/Big Sisters, undated
    - Ron Williams, undated
    - Connecticut River Museum, undated
    - Connecticut Department of Environmental Protection: Utility deregulation, undated
    - Defense authorization v. Environment, 2002
    - Department of Defense v. Environment, 2003
    - Department of Defense Environmental exemptions FY05, undated
    - Climate stewardship, undated
    - Coastal Steward of the Year, 2001
  - Grants files (Gr - Re), undated, 2002-2005 (Box 164)
    - Unidentified, undated; [2 ff]
    - Griswold-Pachaug River Place Elderly Housing, 2003 June 10
    - Groton Fire Department, 2003 April 22
    - Groton Fire Department, Assistance to Firefighters, 2004
    - Groton Fire Department, Assistance to Firefighters-Fire Prevention, 2004 September 16
    - Groton Plane crash, 2003 August 4
    - Groton Public Schools, 2003 June 7
    - Groton utilities, undated
    - Habitat for Humanity, Fitch Area project, 2003 December 3
    - Habitat for Humanity SECT, Davis Farms Community development, 2004 October 8
    - Habitat for Humanity, Brownfields Cleanup, 2005
    - Habitat for Humanity, 2005 January 6
    - Habitat for Humanity or SECT, 2003 September 9
    - Haitian Health Foundation, 2003 January 16
    - Haitian Health Foundation, 2004 January 27
    - Hebron Fire Department, undated
    - Homeland Security-State grant, 2004
    - Homeland Security-State grants, 2005
    - HUD
      - Affordable Housing closing, undated
      - Awards, 2004 January 30
      - Capital Fund Program, 2003-2004
      - Super NOVA, 2005
      - Continuum of Homeless awards, 2003
      - Grants, 2005
    - Improving Literacy through school libraries, New London, 2003 March 26
    - International Children's Conference on the Environment, Tall Ship Invite, 2003 September 19
    - Italian Dramatic Club, 2003 April 17
    - Jewett City, Water and Waste disposal grant, 2004 September 14
    - Junior Colonials Fife and Drum Corps, 2005 March 29
    - Kidsworks, 2003 April 15
    - LaGasse, Kent, 2003 June 30
    - LAMPP, 2003 June 6
    - LAMPP, State Representative DAvid Blackwell, 2002 October 1
    - LEARN, 2004 March 9
    - Ledge Light Health District, Groton, 2004 September 16
    - Ledyard Fire Company, District 1, 2004 March 24
    - Ledyard Fire Department, District 1, 2003 April 22
    - Lisbon Fire Department, 2004 April 2
    - Lisbon Textile Prints, 2004 April 7
    - Livery Limited, undated
    - Logistec USA, 2003 February 28
    - Logistec, New London, 2003 August 22
    - Long Island Sound Study, 2003 October 31
    - Lyman Allyn Art Museum, 2004 March 22
    - Lyme Academy, 2004 June 30
    - Lynde Point Marsh Restoration, 2002 November 22
    - Madison, undated
    - Madison Police Department, Cops in schools, 2003 April 30
    - Manschester Board of Education, HeadStart, 2003 May 1
    - Manchester LAP, 2004 July 12
    - Manchester Memorial Hospital, 2003 September 1
    - Mansfield, 2003 April 25
    - Mansfield Retirement Community, 2004 June 7
    - Marlborough Volunteer Fire Department, 2004
    - Mashantucket Pequot Tribal Police, 2004 September 8
    - Masonicare, 2003 January 21
    - Middlesex Community College EPA TRaining Grant, 2003 May 16
    - Middlesex County Substance Abuse Action Council, undated
    - Mitchell College, 2003 March 5
    - Mortlake Fire Company (Brooklyn), 2004 April 1
    - Mortlake Fire Department, 2003 April 1
    - Muddy Brok Fire Department (Woodstock), 2003 May 9
    - Muddy Brook Fire Department, 2004 April 1
    - Mystic Aquarium, 2004-2005
    - Mystic Color Lab and Kaman Aerospace, 2003 January 22
    - Mystic Fire Department, 2004 April 9
    - NECASA, Drug Free Communities, 2004 July 15
    - New London, Amber Properties Food Market, undated
    - New London, CDBG, 2004 August 9
    - New London, 2004 September 27
    - New London Development Corporation, 2003 June 25
    - New London Police Department, 2003-2004
    - New London POlice Department, Port Security Safety Administration, 2003-2004
    - New Samaritan Housing, Andover, 2004 August 30
    - North Stonington Volunteer Fire Department, 2003
    - Northeast Workforce Investment Board, 2003 July 25
    - Norwich, CDBG, 2003 September 18
    - Norwich, Earmark, 2004 August 26
    - Norwich Heritage Discovery Center conceptual plan, 2003 July 28
    - Norwich Public Schools, 2003 May 16
    - Old Lyme Fire Department, 2003 April 17
    - Old Lyme Fire Department, Assistance to Firefighters, 2004
    - Old Mystic Fire Department, 2004 April 23
    - Old Saybrook, Regional Communications Center, undated
    - Oncology Network of Connecticut, 2004 January 13
    - Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, 2002 November 21
    - Oswegatchie Hills, East Lyme, undated
    - Paul and Lisa Program, Inc., 2003-2004
    - Plainfield Department of POlice Services, 2002 September 25
    - Plainfield, EDA for Lowes property, undated
    - Poquetanuck Volunteer Fire Department, 2004 May 18
    - Preston, Open Space, undated
    - Project Liberty Ship, 2002 September 23
    - Prudence Crandall Museum, 2003 April 1
    - Putnam Fire Department, 2002 October 16
    - Putnam, Town of, 2003 September 29
    - Quinebaug-Shetucket Heritage Corridor, 200-2004; [2 ff]
    - Regional Growth Partnership, Brownfields EPA, 2003 March 13
    - Rose City Senior Center Medicare event, undated
    - Rural Development Workshop, 2003 October 27
    - Rural Health, Connecticut Department of, Regional meeting, 2004 June 2
  - Homeland Security, undated, 2001-2006 (Box 165)
    - Committee on Homeland Security, IIS&TRA budget, 2005 February 16; [2 ff]
    - Using Open-Source Information Effectively, 2005 June 15; [2 ff]
    - "The Role of the Chief Intelligence Officer,", 2005 October 19; [2 ff]
    - "Terrorism Risk Assessment at the Department of Homeland Security,", 2005 November 17; [2 ff]
    - "Examining the Progress of the DHS Chief Intelligence Officer,", 2006 May 24
    - DHS Authorization for FY 2006, 2005 April 27; [3 ff]
    - OSINT Fair, 2005
    - OSINT Literature, undated
    - Avery Point Lighthouse, 2001; [3 ff]
    - U.S. Coast Guard Museum, 2001-2004; [3 ff]
      - Press, undated
      - DeFazio, undated
    - Meetings, 2001-2005
    - Subs, 2005
    - Kelo v. New London, 2005
    - "Standard Serving" of alcohol, 2005
    - U.S. Coast Guard Authorization, HR 2443, 2004; [2 ff]
  - FY 07 Appropriations, undated, 2006 (Box 166)
    - Appropriations, undated
    - L-HHS-Ed, undated
    - TTHUD, undated
    - Mystic Seaport, undated
    - Agriculture, undated
    - Homeland Security, undated
    - Foreign Operations, undated
    - SSJC, undated
    - Town of Norwich, undated
    - East Haddam, undated
    - Asnuntuck Community College, undated
    - Mystic Aquarium, undated
    - Town of Vernon, undated
    - Miltary Quality of Life, undated
    - WHTI, undated
    - S.C. IIS&TRA markup, undated
    - Avian Flu, undated
    - Cape Wind, undated
    - S.C. IIS&TRA Hearing, undated
    - Doncasters (CFIUS), undated
    - 3M, undated
    - DHS Authorization, undated
    - Corrugated Steel, undated
    - Charles W. Morgan (ship), undated
    - Chemical Plant Security, undated
    - Container Security/Retailer perspective, undated
    - Homeland Security/CG, undated
    - HR 5005: DHS creation, undated
    - Port Security, undated
    - Chirico Group, undated
    - FEMA Connecticut specific, undated
    - Terrorism insurance, undated
    - Deepwater, undated
    - Homeland Security Academy, undated
    - DHS grants, undated
    - SAFE Port Act, undated
    - SAFE Port Act hearing, 2006 April 4
    - 3rd Party Issue, undated
    - Uganda, undated
    - Iran, undated
    - Israel, undated
    - China, undated
    - Mongolian Ambassador, undated
    - Geno Auriemma Resolution, undated
  - BRAC, Contracts, SUBASE, USCG, Ct Guard, undated, 2003-2006 (Box 167)
    - Coast Guard, 2005
    - Coast Guard Retirement Homes, 2004
    - Subase New London, MILCON Brief for Representative Simmons, 2005 February 28
    - Meeting with Commanding Officier, Naval Submarine Base New London, 2004 February 23
    - SUBASE New London, 10 year Infrastructure plan, undated
    - Naval Submarine Base, New London, Brief for Rep. Simmons, 2005 August 26
    - Defense, MILCON and Homeland Security, FY 05 Authorization and Appropriations materials, copies 1 and 2, undated; [4 ff]
    - BRAC materials, 2003
    - BRAC materials, 2004; [2 ff]
    - BRAC news articles, 2003-2004
    - BRAC, undated; [3 ff]
    - Overseas Basing Commission, Report of the Commission on Review of the Overseas Military FAcility Structure of the U.S., 2005 August
    - Military Bases; Analysis of DOD's 2005 Selection Process and Recommenatiosn for Base Closures and Realignments, 2005 July
    - District contracts, 2005-2006
    - PECIREP, undated
    - Connecticut National Guard, undated
    - Connecticut Air National Guard, undated
    - Connecticut Homeland Security, undated
    - DeCA Commissary, undated
    - Groton, undated
    - Navy Region Northeast, undated
    - Inauguration Ceremonies invitations, 2005d
    - Newspaper articles, 2004-2005
  - Transportation & Infrastructure Committee files, 2001-2004 (Box 27)
    - Rob T & I transcripts, 2001
    - RR Hearing: Amtrak REform Council Restructuring Plan, 2002 February 14d
    - Amtrak Reauthorization, 2002 April 24
    - Hearing: Amtrak Reform and Accountability Act, 2002 March 6
    - Current Amtrak Issues, 2003 April 30
    - Rail Infrastructure Development and Expansion Act for the 21st century,", 2003 June 25
    - HR 2572, Full committee, "Amtrak Reauthorization Act of 2003,", 2003 June 25
    - Subcommittee on Railroad oversight hearing: Amtrak reform proposals, 2005 September 21
    - TEA 21 Success Stories, Hearing, 2001 November 1
    - Subcommittee Hearing, HR 5455: ExPdite, 2002 October 8
    - Highways: Transit Service/Benefits to U.S. COmmunities, 2002 April 17
    - TEA 21 Intermodalism, 2002 June 18
    - Federal Transit Capital GRants Programs, TEA 21, 2002 June 20
    - Truck Safety Hearing, 2002 September 7
    - TEA 21, Highway Trust Fund and Fuel Taxes, 2002 July 16
    - Highways: SAFE TEA, 2003 May; [2 ff]
    - Full Committee markup, HR 3266, 2004 June 2
    - "Faster and Smarter Funding for First Responders Act,", undated
    - HR 2546, Interstate Driver Equity Act--Good for Connecticut, undated
    - Background checks in the Trucking Industry, undated
    - Full committee markup, HR 1979, Contrct ATC Towers, 2002 April 24
    - Hearing: Integrity of Highway Trust Fund, 2002 March 20
    - Full Committee markup, HR 3930, "WAter Quality Financing Act of 2002,", 2002 March 20
    - Markup, Arming pilots and other...,", 2002 June 26
    - Full committee hearing, HR 2891, To preserve the viability of the U.S. air transportation system, 2001 September 19
    - Full Committee markup, HR 2133, "Aviation Security Technical Corrections and Improvements Act of 2003,", 2003 June 5
    - CG&MT Subcommittee Hearing, Financial Responsibility for Port Security, 2002 March 14
    - Maritime Disaster Family Assistance Act, 2002 June 12
    - Full committee markup, HR 3983, Maritime Transportation AntiTerrorism Act, 2002 March 20
    - Hearing, Port Security, Containers, 2002 March 13
    - CG 03 Budget hearing, undated
    - Subcommittee on Coast Guard Oversight, hearing on: U.S. Coast Guard's move to Homeland Security, 2003 April 1
    - Full Committee markup, HR 3879, "Coast Guard Authorization Act for FY 2005,", 2004 April 21
    - CG&MT Subcommittee hearing, Coast Guard Aurhtorization Act of 2003, 2003 May 22
    - CG&MT Subcommittee hearing, Implementation of the MTSA and HR 3712 and HR 2193, 2004 June 9
  - Submarines, Sub building, Navy, undated, 2005-2006 (Box 169)
    - Littoral Combat Ship (LCS), undated
    - LCS/ADS, undated
    - Navy personnel, undated
    - China, undated
    - PACOM, undated
    - Taiwan Sub meeting, 2006 September 28
    - Republic of China trip, undated
    - Simmons plan--Subs, undated
    - Subs, 2003-2005
    - Readiness--Navy transformation, 2006 April 6
    - NRNE, undated
    - Cook sub, undated
    - Battleships, undated
    - Virginia class, undated
    - Navy posture FY 06, undated
    - Sub caucus, undated
    - Shipbuilding caucus, undated
    - American Shipbuilding Association, Industry Day, 2005 April 20
    - Navy transformation, undated
    - SubForce level briefing, undated
    - Groton/ESCU childcare, undated
    - Depot maintenance--EB, undated
    - ASDS, undated; [3 ff]
    - 2 per year, undated
    - Electric Boat (EB) layoffs/maintenance, undated; [2 ff]
    - EB layoffs--Individuals, undated
    - Rickover, undated
    - Projection Forces conference, undated
    - Projection Forces Subcommittee, U.S. Navy's Future, Submarine Force Structure Hearing, 2006 March 28; [2 ff]
    - Projection Forces Subcommittee, Hearing on DD(X) Destroyer program, 2005 July 19
    - Navy Posture Hearing, 2006 March 3
  - Submarines, Submarine building, Navy, Defense Issues, DSS-OPM transfer, undated, 1981, 2004-2006 (Box 170)
    - SubForce Field Hearing, undated
    - Force Protection Hearing, 2006 February 1
    - Office of Naval Intelligence, Worldwide Maritime Challenges, 2004
    - Options for the Navy's Future Fleet, a CBO study, 2006 May
    - Electric Boat handout package, 2006 August 31
    - John Warner National Defense Authorization Act for FY 07, Conference report to accompany HR 5122, 2006 September 26
    - White Papers, undated
    - Afghanistan, undated
    - Armenia, undated
    - Co-Sponsor 108 (1 and 2), undated
    - Co-sponsor forms, undated
    - Agency response, undated
    - FY 05 Intelligence authorization, undated
    - Up-armored HMMWVS, undated
    - 767 Tanker lease, Boeing, undated
    - Aircraft, Lockheed Martin, undated
    - Ports leg., undated
    - Dubai/Doncasters, undated
    - FTF, undated
    - HASC Budget, undated
    - Revised Deepwater Implementation Plan, 2005 March 25
    - Israel, undated
    - Boeing C-17 Economic Impact information, undated
    - JSF engine, undated
    - CH-53X, undated
    - Marine One, undated
    - Offsets/EU Defense trade, undated
    - Transfer, undated
    - NSPS, undated
    - Reserves, undated
    - Interrogations, 1981
    - GTMO, undated
    - NUWC BRAC leave, undated
    - NUWC/BRAC pay/leave, constituents, undated
    - DSS-OPM transfer issue, undated; [2 ff]
  - Defense issues, DSS-OPM Transfer, Energy, undated, 2005-2006 (Box 171)
    - DSS-OPM, undated
    - Professional Services Council, undated
    - DSS-OPM cleareances, undated
    - DSS to OPM: DSS, SEcurity clearance, UWVs, Defense transformation, undated; [6 ff]
    - Aircraft, undated
    - F-22, undated
    - Broadwater, undated; [3 ff]
    - Broadwater: Coast Guard-WSR, 2006 September
    - Nuclear security: HR 6 conference, undated
    - Nuclear security, undated
    - Duncan Broatch projects, undated
    - Energy Bill (law), undated
    - HR 6, 2005; [8 ff]
    - ANWAR budget, undated
  - Energy, Transportation, undated, 2003 (Box 172)
    - HR 6, undated; [2 ff]
    - LIHEAP, undated; [3 ff]
    - Nuclear--Dominion, undated
    - Nuclear--Millstone, undated
    - Nuclear energy--Areva, undated
    - Nuclear waste--Yucca, undated
    - Nuclear waste--Dry cask storage, undated
    - Connecticut Yankee Atomic Power Company, undated
    - Energy, 109th Congress, undated; [3 ff]
    - NSR, undated
    - NRG Project, Montville, CT, undated
    - NORA, undated
    - CT Municipal Electric Energy, undated
    - Energy events, undated
    - FY 2007 Appropriations, member requests and support letters, undated; [4 ff]
    - Congressional Record, 2003 November 25
  - Transportation, FY 2004 and FY 2005 appropriations, DHS 2005 authorization, Environment (Box 173)
    - TEA 21 Projects, undated; [4 ff]
    - Highway Bill go-to-book, undated; [3 ff]
    - Requests: master copy, undated; [2 ff]
    - Requests: HQ copy, undated; [2 ff]
    - Letter sign ons, undated; [3 ff]
    - DHS authorization, 2005; [2ff]
    - Healthy Forests Act, undated; [2 ff]
    - Simmons and the Environment, 109th Congress, undated
    - League of COnservation Voters book, 2004 July
    - Climate Stewardship Act Resource Book, undated
    - League of COnservation Voters, undated; [2ff]
  - Environment, undated, 2002-2006 (Box 174)
    - Environment, 109th Congress, undated; [4 ff]
    - Mute Swans, 2002-2004; [4 ff]
    - Coastal Management Plan, 2006
    - Quniebaug-Shetucket Historical Corridor, 2006; [2 ff]
    - Eightmile River, undated; [5 ff]
    - Odds and ends from Lise, undated
    - Glacier Society, undated
    - InterRoyal Mill, undated
    - MTBE, undated
    - The Nature COnservancy, undated
    - EPA Wetlands/CWA rulemaking, undated
    - U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service, undated
    - Forest Legacy Program: Stonehouse Brook..., undated
    - Ozone Standard, undated
    - Primate Safety Act, undated
    - Sierra Club, undated
    - TRI, undated
  - News Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box 175)
    - 2004 February - March, [2 ff]
    - 2004 March
    - 2004 March - April
    - 2004 December
    - 2004 December - 2005 January
    - 2005 January, [2 ff]
    - 2005 May - June, [2 ff]
    - 2005 June, [2 ff]
    - 2005 June - July
    - 2005 July, [5 ff]
    - 2005 July - August